<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cooking Recipe</string>
    <string name="start_title">Don’t think about what to cook - in our application you can find interesting recipes for every day</string>
    <string name="start_program">Start Program</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="test">test</string>
    <string name="_12_minute">12 minute</string>
    <string name="_2">2</string>
    <string name="_120_kcal">120 kcal</string>
    <string name="good_morning">Good Morning</string>
    <string name="russell_sprout">Russell Sprout</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="recommended">Recommended</string>
    <string name="ingredients">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="start_cooking">Start Cooking</string>
    <string name="all_recipes">All Recipes</string>
    <string name="net_carbs">Net Carbs</string>
    <string name="fat">Fat</string>
    <string name="protein">Protein</string>
    <string name="recipe">Recipe</string>
    <string name="done">done</string>
    <string name="details">See All</string>
    <string name="fish">Fish</string>
    <string name="vegetables">Vegetables</string>
    <string name="meat">Meat</string>
    <string name="dinner">Dinner</string>
    <string name="lunch">Lunch</string>
    <string name="grilled_salmon">Grilled Salmon</string>
    <string name="desc1_1">Grilled salmon with vegetables and lemon is an exquisite dish that will surely please all fish lovers. Juicy salmon is prepared on the grill in combination with fresh vegetables and aromatic lemon.</string>
    <string name="desc1_2">Grilled salmon with spices and lemon</string>
    <string name="desc1_3">Tuna steak with lemon and soy sauce</string>
    <string name="desc1_4">Salmon with mashed potatoes and herb sauce</string>
    <string name="desc1_5">Eel baked in teriyaki sauce</string>
    <string name="desc1_6">Shrimp fried with lemon and garlic</string>
    <string name="desc1_7">Mussels in creamy sauce with garlic and parsley</string>
    <string name="desc1_8">Tuna with orange glaze and grapefruit salad</string>
    <string name="desc1_9">Sardines with greens and lemon</string>
    <string name="desc1_10">Spicy tuna curry with coconut milk</string>
    <string name="desc2_1">Broccoli baked with Parmesan and spices. This simple and delicious dish makes an excellent side or appetizer.</string>
    <string name="desc2_2">Salad with cucumbers, tomatoes, and feta cheese. This salad enriches your lunch or dinner with fresh vegetables and tender cheese.</string>
    <string name="desc2_3">Potatoes baked with cheese and cream. This rich and hearty dish makes an excellent choice for dinner.</string>
    <string name="desc2_4">Traditional French ratatouille with vegetables. This vibrant and flavorful dish brings the authentic taste of France to your table.</string>
    <string name="desc2_5">Potatoes stuffed with vegetables and cheese. This tasty and hearty dish is prepared with minimal effort.</string>
    <string name="desc2_6">Fragrant rice cooked with vegetables and spices. This delicious dish is suitable as a side or main course.</string>
    <string name="desc2_7">Creamy spinach soup with potatoes. This soup makes an excellent start to your dinner.</string>
    <string name="desc2_8">Sweet potatoes baked with honey and cinnamon. This dessert is a perfect way to end your dinner.</string>
    <string name="desc2_9">Cauliflower with bacon and ranch dressing. This salad combines freshness and rich flavor.</string>
    <string name="desc2_10">Aromatic soup with pumpkin, ginger, and coconut milk. An ideal choice for the cold season.</string>
    <string name="desc3_1">Juicy beef steak, grilled with aromatic spices and herbs. This dish will surely delight meat lovers with its rich flavor and tender steak texture. The combination of spicy spices and aromatic herbs gives this steak a special twist.</string>
    <string name="desc3_2">Chicken wings cooked in BBQ sauce with a pleasant spiciness. This dish is perfect for parties and outdoor gatherings. Juicy and flavorful wings will delight all your guests.</string>
    <string name="desc3_3">Pork cutlet baked with honey-mustard sauce, balancing sweetness and spiciness. This dish combines the tenderness of pork with the unique flavors of honey and mustard. Perfect for special occasions and outdoor dinners.</string>
    <string name="desc3_4">Italian Carbonara dish prepared with salmon and creamy sauce. This dish is exceptionally tender and flavorful, with a rich creamy sauce. An excellent choice for special moments and outdoor dinners.</string>
    <string name="desc3_5">Juicy meat patties with a cheese filling. This dish is perfect for a festive dinner or a quick weekday meal. Juicy and flavorful, they will add variety to your table.</string>
    <string name="desc3_6">Homemade fried chicken nuggets. This is an American classic that will appeal to both children and adults. With a crispy coating and juicy meat, they are perfect for snacking.</string>
    <string name="desc3_7">Pork ribs baked in BBQ sauce. This dish features juicy and aromatic meat with a sweet and spicy glaze. Ideal for outdoor dinners and parties.</string>
    <string name="desc3_8">Spicy beef meatballs baked in tomato sauce. This dish combines the tenderness of meat with the aroma of tomato sauce and spices. Perfect for family dinners.</string>
    <string name="desc3_9">Roasted turkey with aromatic cranberry sauce. This dish is perfect for festive dinners and special occasions. The tender turkey meat and sweet cranberry sauce create a unique flavor combination.</string>
    <string name="desc3_10">Flavorful noodles with chicken and fresh vegetables. This dish combines tender chicken breast, crispy vegetables, and a flavorful sauce. It\'s perfect for quick and satisfying lunches or dinners.</string>
    <string name="desc4_1">Italian Carbonara dish prepared with salmon and creamy sauce. This dish is exceptionally tender and flavorful, with a rich creamy sauce. An excellent choice for special moments and outdoor dinners.</string>
    <string name="desc4_2">A delicious steak with a tender mushroom sauce is an excellent choice for meat lovers. Juicy meat and aromatic sauce create an unforgettable dish.</string>
    <string name="desc4_3">Baked chicken with seasonal vegetables is a great choice for a healthy dinner. Chicken protein and vitamins in vegetables make your dinner balanced and delicious.</string>
    <string name="desc4_4">Pork baked with apples and caramel sauce is an amazing combination of sweet and tender meat with tart apples. Perfect for festive dinners.</string>
    <string name="desc4_5">Beef marinated in teriyaki sauce and cooked to perfection. Perfect for lovers of juicy meat and Asian cuisine.</string>
    <string name="desc4_6">Fish fillet baked with lemon and herbs is a light and refreshing dish for those who care about their health. Fish is rich in protein and essential nutrients.</string>
    <string name="desc4_7">Classic Chicken Kiev cutlets with tender chicken mince and butter inside. This dish will delight all chicken lovers and leave no one indifferent.</string>
    <string name="desc4_8">Pork ribs baked with flavorful barbecue sauce. A dish with a rich taste and appetizing aroma, perfect for picnics and outdoor gatherings.</string>
    <string name="desc4_9">Appetizing pasta with meat sauce is a classic Italian dish that the whole family will enjoy. Juicy meat filling and aromatic spices will make your dinner unforgettable.</string>
    <string name="desc4_10">Pork cutlets are a simple and delicious meat dish. Tender pork meat with aromatic spices will please all meat enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="desc5_1">Refreshing Greek pita light salad with cucumbers, tomatoes, and feta. It\'s perfect for a light lunch on a hot day.</string>
    <string name="desc5_2">Tuna salad with a mix of greens and olive oil. This meal is an excellent source of protein and healthy fats.</string>
    <string name="desc5_3">Chicken sandwich with avocado and spices. This dish combines a wonderful and rich flavor.</string>
    <string name="desc5_4">Vegetable omelette - a light and hearty lunch. Perfect for those who watch their figure.</string>
    <string name="desc5_5">Shrimp salad with avocado. This light lunch is rich in protein and healthy fats.</string>
    <string name="desc5_6">Quinoa with vegetables and greens - a perfect choice for vegetarians. Rich in protein and nutrients.</string>
    <string name="desc5_7">Turkey sandwich with red onion. This light lunch is rich in protein and low in calories.</string>
    <string name="desc5_8">Pasta with mushrooms and creamy sauce. This dish is perfect for lunch and combines a rich taste with a creamy sauce.</string>
    <string name="desc5_9">Traditional Hungarian goulash soup with meat and vegetables. This hearty and aromatic dish is perfect for a cold day.</string>
    <string name="desc5_10">Tuna vegetable salad with tomatoes, cucumbers, olives, and olive oil. This light lunch is rich in protein and low in calories.</string>
    <string name="salmon_fillet">Salmon fillet</string>
    <string name="tomatoes">Tomatoes</string>
    <string name="broccoli">Broccoli</string>
    <string name="lemon">Lemon</string>
    <string name="salt_and_pepper_to_taste">Salt and pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="recipe1_1">1. Prepare the salmon fillet, season with salt and pepper to taste. Squeeze the lemon juice.\n2. Preheat the grill. Grill the salmon with vegetables until cooked, occasionally drizzling with lemon juice.\n3. Serve with the remaining lemon and seasonings to taste.</string>
    <string name="recipe1_2">1. Prepare the salmon and season with spices. Ignite the grill and grill the salmon until cooked.\n2. Serve with lemon and garlic.</string>
    <string name="recipe1_3">1. Prepare the tuna and season with soy sauce, garlic, and pepper. Sear in a pan until desired doneness.\n2. Serve with lemon and greens.</string>
    <string name="recipe1_4">1. Prepare the salmon and pan-fry until done. Prepare mashed potatoes.\n2. Serve the salmon with mashed potatoes and a herb sauce.</string>
    <string name="recipe1_5">1. Bake eel in teriyaki sauce with garlic and ginger until done.\n2. Serve sprinkled with herbs.</string>
    <string name="recipe1_6">1. Fry the shrimp with garlic in olive oil until golden brown.\n2. Drizzle with lemon juice and sprinkle with parsley and pepper.</string>
    <string name="recipe1_7">1. Heat a skillet, add garlic and sauté until fragrant. Add mussels and cook until they open.\n2. Pour in white wine and add cream. Simmer until the sauce thickens.\n3. Serve, sprinkled with parsley.</string>
    <string name="recipe1_8">1. Sear tuna until desired doneness. Prepare a glaze from orange juice, honey, and soy sauce.\n2. Mix oranges and grapefruits for the salad.\n3. Serve tuna with orange glaze on grapefruit salad.</string>
    <string name="recipe1_9">1. Fry sardines with greens and lemon in olive oil until done.\n2. Serve, sprinkled with greens and seasoned to taste.</string>
    <string name="recipe1_10">1. Sear tuna until golden brown. Set aside.\n2. In the same pan, sauté garlic and ginger. Add curry paste and sauté a bit more.\n3. Add coconut milk and vegetables. Simmer until done.\n4. Serve curry with tuna pieces.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_1">1. Cut broccoli into florets. Drizzle with olive oil and sprinkle with Parmesan and spices.\n2. Bake in a preheated oven until golden brown.\n3. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_2">1. Dice cucumbers, tomatoes, onions, and feta cheese.\n2. Add olives and olive oil. Mix.\n3. Serve as a snack or side dish.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_3">1. Slice potatoes thinly and mix with garlic and spices.\n2. Pour cream over and sprinkle with cheese.\n3. Bake until golden brown.\n4. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_4">1. Slice the vegetables into thin rounds.\n2. Sauté them in tomato sauce with garlic and spices.\n3. Cook until the vegetables are tender.\n4. Serve as a side or main dish.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_5">1. Prepare potato halves.\n2. Fill them with tomatoes, feta cheese, and olives.\n3. Bake until golden brown.\n4. Serve as a side or appetizer.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_6">1. Sauté onions and spices.\n2. Add rice and cook until it becomes translucent.\n3. Add vegetables and cook until tender.\n4. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_7">1. Sauté onions and potatoes.\n2. Add spinach and cook until tender.\n3. Puree the soup and add cream and spices.\n4. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_8">1. Cut sweet potatoes and mix with olive oil, honey, and cinnamon.\n2. Bake in the oven until tender.\n3. Serve hot as a side or dessert.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_9">1. Boil cauliflower until tender.\n2. Sauté bacon.\n3. Mix cauliflower with bacon and ranch dressing.\n4. Serve as a side or salad.</string>
    <string name="recipe2_10">1. Dice pumpkin and sauté with onions, garlic, and ginger.\n2. Add coconut milk and simmer until tender.\n3. Puree the soup and add spices.\n4. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_1">1. Prepare the beef steak and marinade with spices and herbs.\n2. Grill the steak to your desired level of doneness.\n3. Serve hot with seasonings.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_2">1. Marinate chicken wings in BBQ sauce with paprika, garlic, and salt.\n2. Grill them until crispy.\n3. Serve hot with vegetables.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_3">1. Marinate pork cutlet in honey-mustard sauce with garlic and salt.\n2. Bake until golden brown.\n3. Serve hot with a side dish.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_5">1. Cook spaghetti.\n2. Sauté salmon in a pan, add cream, parmesan, egg, and garlic.\n3. Mix and combine with cooked spaghetti.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_4">1. Prepare the ground meat, add onion, spices, and breadcrumbs.\n2. Form patties, placing a piece of cheese inside each.\n3. Fry until golden brown.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_6">1. Coat chicken pieces in egg and breadcrumbs with spices.\n2. Fry until golden brown in vegetable oil.\n3. Serve with your favorite sauce.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_7">1. Marinate pork ribs in BBQ sauce with spices, garlic, and salt.\n2. Bake until done in the oven.\n3. Serve hot with vegetables.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_8">1. Mix ground beef with onion, spices, and salt, and form meatballs.\n2. Pour tomato sauce over them and bake in the oven.\n3. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_9">1. Prepare the turkey, roast it with rosemary, garlic, and salt.\n2. Serve with cranberry sauce.</string>
    <string name="recipe3_10">1. Sauté chicken breast and vegetables, add soy sauce.\n2. Cook noodles and combine with the other ingredients.\n3. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_1">1. Cook spaghetti.\n2. Sauté salmon in a pan, add cream, parmesan, egg, and garlic.\n3. Mix and combine with cooked spaghetti.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_2">1. Sear the steak in a pan to your desired level of doneness.\n2. Prepare a mushroom sauce with mushrooms, onion, garlic, and cream.\n3. Serve the steak with the mushroom sauce.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_3">1. Prepare chicken breast and vegetables.\n2. Bake them in the oven until done.\n3. Serve hot as the main dish.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_4">1. Prepare pork, slice apples.\n2. Bake pork with apples, drizzling with caramel sauce and spices.\n3. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_5">1. Marinate beef in teriyaki sauce, garlic, and ginger.\n2. Sear the meat to your desired level of doneness.\n3. Serve with greens.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_6">1. Prepare fish fillet, season with spices and garlic.\n2. Bake with lemon and herbs until done.\n3. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_7">1. Form chicken mince into cutlets, hiding butter inside.\n2. Coat with breadcrumbs and fry until golden brown.\n3. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_8">1. Marinate pork ribs in barbecue sauce, garlic, and spices.\n2. Bake until done in the oven or on the grill.\n3. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_9">1. Sauté minced meat with onion and garlic, add tomatoes and spices.\n2. Cook spaghetti and combine them with the meat sauce.\n3. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe4_10">1. Form pork cutlets, season with spices and coat with breadcrumbs.\n2. Fry until golden brown.\n3. Serve hot.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_1">1. Chop cucumbers and tomatoes, mix with feta and herbs.\n2. Fill pita bread with the mixture and add olive oil.\n3. Roll up the pita and serve.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_2">1. Sear the tuna in a pan until golden brown.\n2. Mix the mixed greens with olive oil, lemon juice, pepper, and salt.\n3. Place the tuna on the salad and serve.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_3">1. Sear the chicken fillet until golden brown.\n2. Mix mayonnaise, mustard, and spices for the sauce.\n3. Assemble the sandwich: lettuce leaves, chicken fillet, avocado, and tomatoes. Drizzle with the sauce.\n4. Serve with vegetable chips.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_4">1. Beat eggs with milk.\n2. Sauté vegetables and herbs, then add eggs.\n3. Serve with cheese and tomatoes.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_5">1. Sauté the shrimp in a pan with olive oil and lemon juice.\n2. Mix lettuce, avocado, and shrimp. Drizzle with a sauce made from olive oil, lemon juice, pepper, and salt.\n3. Serve as a light lunch.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_6">1. Cook quinoa.\n2. Sauté vegetables and greens with spices.\n3. Mix with quinoa and serve.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_7">1. Sauté the turkey in a pan with mustard, lemon juice, and spices.\n2. Assemble the sandwich: lettuce leaves, turkey, red onion. Drizzle with the sauce.\n3. Serve with vegetable chips.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_8">1. Cook pasta.\n2. Sauté mushrooms and garlic in a pan, then add cream and cheese.\n3. Serve with pasta and garnish with parsley.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_9">1. Sauté beef with onion and paprika.\n2. Add potatoes, tomatoes, and spices. Cook until the vegetables are tender.\n3. Serve hot with a piece of bread.</string>
    <string name="recipe5_10">1. Sauté the tuna in a pan with olive oil.\n2. Mix mixed greens, tomatoes, cucumbers, and olives.\n3. Place the tuna on the salad and serve.</string>
    <string name="seafood">Seafood</string>
    <string name="_20_minutes">20 minutes</string>
    <string name="_280_kcal">280 kcal</string>
    <string name="grilled_salmon_">Grilled Salmon with Spices</string>
    <string name="salmon">Salmon</string>
    <string name="garlic">Garlic</string>
    <string name="olive_oil">Olive oil</string>
    <string name="spices">Spices</string>
    <string name="tuna_steak">Tuna Steak</string>
    <string name="tuna">Tuna</string>
    <string name="soy_sauce">Soy sauce</string>
    <string name="pepper">Pepper</string>
    <string name="_15_minutes">15 minutes</string>
    <string name="_320_kcal">320 kcal</string>
    <string name="salmon_with">Salmon with Mashed Potatoes</string>
    <string name="potatoes">Potatoes</string>
    <string name="milk">Milk</string>
    <string name="herbs">Herbs</string>
    <string name="salt">Salt</string>
    <string name="_30_minutes">30 minutes</string>
    <string name="_380_kcal">380 kcal</string>
    <string name="eel_in_teriyaki_sauce">Eel in Teriyaki Sauce</string>
    <string name="eel">Eel</string>
    <string name="teriyaki_sauce">Teriyaki sauce</string>
    <string name="ginger">Ginger</string>
    <string name="_25_minutes">25 minutes</string>
    <string name="_310_kcal">310 kcal</string>
    <string name="shrimp_with">Shrimp with Lemon and Garlic</string>
    <string name="shrimp">Shrimp</string>
    <string name="parsley">Parsley</string>
    <string name="_180_kcal">180 kcal</string>
    <string name="mussels_in_creamy_sauce">Mussels in Creamy Sauce</string>
    <string name="mussels">Mussels</string>
    <string name="cream">Cream</string>
    <string name="white_wine">White wine</string>
    <string name="_240_kcal">240 kcal</string>
    <string name="tuna_with_orange_glaze">Tuna with Orange Glaze</string>
    <string name="oranges">Oranges</string>
    <string name="grapefruits">Grapefruits</string>
    <string name="honey">Honey</string>
    <string name="sardines_with_greens">Sardines with Greens</string>
    <string name="sardines">Sardines</string>
    <string name="greens">Greens</string>
    <string name="tuna_curry">Tuna Curry</string>
    <string name="curry_paste">Curry paste</string>
    <string name="coconut_milk">Coconut milk</string>
    <string name="_340_kcal">340 kcal</string>
    <string name="broccoli_with_parmesan">Broccoli with Parmesan</string>
    <string name="parmesan">Parmesan</string>
    <string name="_110_kcal">110 kcal</string>
    <string name="greek_salad">Greek Salad</string>
    <string name="cucumbers">Cucumbers</string>
    <string name="feta_cheese">Feta Cheese</string>
    <string name="olives">Olives</string>
    <string name="onion">Onion</string>
    <string name="salads">Salads</string>
    <string name="_160_kcal">160 kcal</string>
    <string name="potato_gratin">Potato Gratin</string>
    <string name="cheese">Cheese</string>
    <string name="_45_minutes">45 minutes</string>
    <string name="ratatouille">Ratatouille</string>
    <string name="eggplant">Eggplant</string>
    <string name="zucchini">Zucchini</string>
    <string name="bell_pepper">Bell Pepper</string>
    <string name="tomato_sauce">Tomato Sauce</string>
    <string name="_220_kcal">220 kcal</string>
    <string name="greek_stuffed_bake">Greek Stuffed Bake</string>
    <string name="_40_minutes">40 minutes</string>
    <string name="_260_kcal">260 kcal</string>
    <string name="vegetable_rice">Vegetable Rice</string>
    <string name="rice">Rice</string>
    <string name="carrots">Carrots</string>
    <string name="peas">Peas</string>
    <string name="spinach_soup">Spinach Soup</string>
    <string name="spinach">Spinach</string>
    <string name="soups">Soups</string>
    <string name="_200_kcal">200 kcal</string>
    <string name="baked_sweet_potatoes">Baked Sweet Potatoes</string>
    <string name="sweet_potatoes">Sweet Potatoes</string>
    <string name="cinnamon">Cinnamon</string>
    <string name="_35_minutes">35 minutes</string>
    <string name="cauliflower_salad">Cauliflower Salad</string>
    <string name="cauliflower">Cauliflower</string>
    <string name="bacon">Bacon</string>
    <string name="ranch_dressing">Ranch Dressing</string>
    <string name="pumpkin_soup">Pumpkin Soup</string>
    <string name="pumpkin">Pumpkin</string>
    <string name="beef_steak">Beef Steak</string>
    <string name="rosemary">Rosemary</string>
    <string name="thyme">Thyme</string>
    <string name="spicy_bbq_wings">Spicy BBQ Wings</string>
    <string name="chicken_wings">Chicken wings</string>
    <string name="bbq_sauce">BBQ sauce</string>
    <string name="paprika">Paprika</string>
    <string name="_250_kcal">250 kcal</string>
    <string name="pork_with_honey_and_mustard">Pork with Honey and Mustard</string>
    <string name="pork_cutlet">Pork cutlet</string>
    <string name="mustard">Mustard</string>
    <string name="_330_kcal">330 kcal</string>
    <string name="carbonara">Carbonara</string>
    <string name="spaghetti">Spaghetti</string>
    <string name="egg">Egg</string>
    <string name="cheese_stuffed_burgers">Cheese-Stuffed Burgers</string>
    <string name="ground_meat">Ground meat</string>
    <string name="breadcrumbs">Breadcrumbs</string>
    <string name="chicken_nuggets">Chicken Nuggets</string>
    <string name="chicken_pieces">Chicken pieces</string>
    <string name="sauce_of_your_choice">Sauce of your choice</string>
    <string name="bbq_ribs">BBQ Ribs</string>
    <string name="pork_ribs">Pork ribs</string>
    <string name="_2_hours">2 hours</string>
    <string name="_360_kcal">360 kcal</string>
    <string name="beef_meatballs">Beef Meatballs</string>
    <string name="ground_beef">Ground beef</string>
    <string name="turkey_with_cranberry_sauce">Turkey with Cranberry Sauce</string>
    <string name="turkey">Turkey</string>
    <string name="cranberry_sauce">Cranberry sauce</string>
    <string name="_350_kcal">350 kcal</string>
    <string name="chicken_and_vegetable_noodles">Chicken and Vegetable Noodles</string>
    <string name="chicken_breast">Chicken breast</string>
    <string name="noodles">Noodles</string>
    <string name="steak_with_mushroom_sauce">Steak with Mushroom Sauce</string>
    <string name="steak">Steak</string>
    <string name="mushrooms">Mushrooms</string>
    <string name="_450_kcal">450 kcal</string>
    <string name="chicken_with_vegetables">Chicken with Vegetables</string>
    <string name="pork_with_apples">Pork with Apples</string>
    <string name="pork">Pork</string>
    <string name="apples">Apples</string>
    <string name="caramel_sauce">Caramel sauce</string>
    <string name="beef_teriyaki">Beef Teriyaki</string>
    <string name="beef">Beef</string>
    <string name="fish_fillet_with_lemon">Fish Fillet with Lemon</string>
    <string name="fish_fillet">Fish fillet</string>
    <string name="_230_kcal">230 kcal</string>
    <string name="chicken_kiev_cutlets">Chicken Kiev Cutlets</string>
    <string name="chicken_mince">Chicken mince</string>
    <string name="butter">Butter</string>
    <string name="bbq_pork_ribs">BBQ Pork Ribs</string>
    <string name="barbecue_sauce">Barbecue sauce</string>
    <string name="_60_minutes">60 minutes</string>
    <string name="_420_kcal">420 kcal</string>
    <string name="pasta_with_meat_sauce">Pasta with Meat Sauce</string>
    <string name="minced_meat">Minced meat</string>
    <string name="pork_cutlets">Pork Cutlets</string>
    <string name="greek_pita_light">Greek Pita Light</string>
    <string name="pita_bread">Pita bread</string>
    <string name="feta">Feta</string>
    <string name="_10_minutes">10 minutes</string>
    <string name="tuna_salad">Tuna Salad</string>
    <string name="mixed_greens">Mixed greens</string>
    <string name="lemon_juice">Lemon juice</string>
    <string name="chicken_sandwich">Chicken Sandwich</string>
    <string name="chicken_fillet">Chicken fillet</string>
    <string name="avocado">Avocado</string>
    <string name="lettuce_leaves">Lettuce leaves</string>
    <string name="mayonnaise">Mayonnaise</string>
    <string name="sandwiches">Sandwiches</string>
    <string name="vegetable_omelette">Vegetable Omelette</string>
    <string name="eggs">Eggs</string>
    <string name="egg_dishes">Egg Dishes</string>
    <string name="shrimp_salad">Shrimp Salad</string>
    <string name="lettuce">Lettuce</string>
    <string name="_300_kcal">300 kcal</string>
    <string name="quinoa_with_vegetables">Quinoa with Vegetables</string>
    <string name="quinoa">Quinoa</string>
    <string name="turkey_sandwich">Turkey Sandwich</string>
    <string name="red_onion">Red onion</string>
    <string name="pasta_with_mushrooms">Pasta with Mushrooms</string>
    <string name="pasta">Pasta</string>
    <string name="goulash_soup">Goulash Soup</string>
    <string name="tuna_vegetable_salad">Tuna Vegetable Salad</string>
</resources>